Andy Williams and the NBC Kids Search for Santa is a
family, comedy film directed by Dwight Hemion.
Andy and the NBC kids search for Santa, starring from Finland.
Self, played by Andy Williams.
Self, played by Tempestt Bledsoe.
Self, played by Lisa Bonet.
Self, played by Mindy Cohn.
Self, played by Casey Ellison.
Self, played by Ami Foster.
This is a list of television productions produced by Universal Television and other NBCUniversal-owned
companies, including television series, streaming television series, and television films.
The film explores themes of singing, finland,
christmas, christmas special, christmas carols.
The tone is lighthearted.